And I did that. And the result was
that I ended up with 20 ,000 words.
And then I had no idea what to do with
it.
And I think what I realize now is that
I'd fallen for a kind of Hollywood
idea
of what writing a book is.
But I need new book stems and mine
with both hands.
You know that the author, like, of a
Hollywood idea of a book is they sit
at
a table and they go like this.
And then there's a montage and, like,
the seasons change around them.
And the manuscript gets higher and
higher and higher.
And then at the end, they've written
the thing, right?
And I have this kind of naive idea
that that's how writing a book worked.
And so when I got to 20 ,000 words and
it wasn't a fully formed book, I
didn't know what to do next.
I was kind of stuck. And so what I did
was I salt for six years.
I didn't really go near it again for
six years.